### Hello

## I'm Jonathan Disla (John)

(321) 330-5852

jon.disla@gmail.com / https://johndisla.com

## Skills

Vast array of web development skills, starting in HTML, CSS (Sass) to build responsive content from designs. Image manipulation and sizing with Photoshop. Modify content with CMS such as Wordpress ecommerce and other site categories. Website integration, migration and deployment. Github project management version control. Freelance and customer service experience.

# **Experience**

January 2019 - PRESENT

#### **Buildisite.com** - Web Developer Freelancer

- Assist particular clients with their online presence goals
- Wordpress design and implementation
- Hosting and migration
- Adhere to client specifications in projects
- Ecommer (Woocommerce)
- Github version control
- HTML/CSS, Javascript and PHP

July 2017 - PRESENT

## Spectrum, Orlando FL - Technical Support

- Maintain focus with customer interaction
- Speak clearly with very simple language for comprehension
- Create reports with accuracy

January 2017 - July 2017

#### **Developer Intern** - *The King's Academy*

- Ecommerce
- Oversee, control and update the online presence
- Development/Design
- Update and maintain the site as necessary to meet business needs
- HTML Emails
- Assist with servers

# **Education**

January 2018 - July 2018

UCF, Florida - Certification web development

Six month continuing education program for web technologies such as Html, Css, Javascript, Git, Terminal, Object Oriented Programming, APIs, AJAX and PHP.

January 2017 - Present

Valencia College, Florida - Programming and Analysis